# question_data = [
#     {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.",
#      "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, "
#              "you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, "
#              "you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
#     {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.",
#      "answer": "False"},
#     {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
# ]

question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "Amazon acquired Twitch in August 2014 for $970 million dollars.",
                  "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In &quot;Team Fortress 2&quot;, the &quot;Bill&#039;s Hat&quot; is a reference to the game &quot;Dota 2&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "The Sniper&#039;s SMG in Team Fortress 2, was originally intended to be the Scout&#039;s primary weapon.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Cave Crawler&quot; will attack you.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In Rocket League, you can play Basketball.", "correct_answer": "True",
                  "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "&quot;Return to Castle Wolfenstein&quot; was the only game of the Wolfenstein series where you don&#039;t play as William &quot;B.J.&quot; Blazkowicz.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In the Season One Championship of &quot;League of Legends&quot;, the highest achievable rank was Diamond.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In the game &quot;Until Dawn&quot; Emily is the only playable character who can be killed by another playable character directly.",
                  "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                 {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                  "question": "In &quot;Resident Evil&quot;, only Chris has access to the grenade launcher.",
                  "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
